What are our triggers for the market?
Vamakshi, our colleague, is associated with this to give bureau in a big way.
Vamakshi, please
tell me where to put it. Sir, let's
start
with some important global events. So tomorrow
we will focus on its details, sales data.
Apart from this, if we look at it, from the global
learning point of view, we will focus on Bank
of America Ltd and Mogan Stock. If
we talk about Nifty companies,
IndusInd Bank will present its results and
due to this, we see that IndusInd
Bank will be in our sight. Apart from this, there are many
big names like ICC
Fox, ICC Prudential, Mahindra
Automotive, Etta and PolyCap India.
All these companies will also present their numbers tomorrow
and due to this, these software should definitely be on your radar. So
finally, these were all the important
triggers and events. You should be on your radar.
Thank you very much for the training session.